Florence Hollis and Rosemary Ross Reynolds Papers, 1863-1987
Sophia Smith Collection, Smith College
- Series VII. TYPOLOGY RESEARCH (194[?]-1986), 4 ft., 3 in.
  To develop and test the typology, Hollis gathered data from counseling sessions recorded in greater than usual detail, and this material is found in the third section. At least nine records with corresponding code sheets from the early 1960s are housed in the series. In addition, there are tape recordings with corresponding interview data and diagnostic records of marital counseling sessions from the mid 1960s, gathered from family service agencies in St. Louis and Philadelphia.
  Hollis's papers and speeches about the typology are found in the fourth section. Both social work students and experienced clinicians adopted it for use. Hollis served as an advisor or consultant to several students who explored the typology in their major works. These include Edward Mullen, Francis Turner, and F. Louise Boatman, and Mitzi Montgomery, whose doctoral theses and related papers and publications are housed in the fifth section. The typology also generated interest in more distant points in the United States and abroad, and the queries and findings of this group are also included here.
- Series VIII. NOTES ON SELECTED DOCUMENTS ca. 1930-1986, 4 in.
  The series is arranged in the order in which Hollis assembled it, by broad categories.
  This series, consisting of eighteen folders, five cassette tapes and an accompanying key, was created by Florence Hollis in 1985 and 1986 to help elucidate some of the early material in her papers. Hollis selected certain documents from the collection, had them copied and added explanatory notes in writing and on tape to make the material more accessible to researchers. Quite often the tapes record Hollis reading the less legible segments of the document aloud, although some of the cassettes do include background information about how and where the material was used. Most of the material from the tapes has been transcribed by the Sophia Smith Collection and housed in the appropriate folder.
  Folders 1-4 contain copies of teaching notes from the 1930s with partial transcriptions and/or commentary. Folders 5-16 contain copies of notes for various speeches from 1930 to 1940 with accompanying transcription and/or commentary. Folder 17 contains copies of case notes and folder 18 provides a copy of the notes on Helen Perlman's book with transcription in the margins. The five tapes include material related to all 18 folders. The original documents have been integrated into appropriate series in the collection.
- Series IX. PHOTOGRAPHS 1901-1987, 10 in.
  This series is divided into the photograph collections of Florence Hollis and Rosemary Reynolds. The series contains snapshots and more formal portraits of family members, friends and colleagues. Photographs of Betsey Libbey, Dame Eileen Younghusband and other notable social workers are included in the Forence Hollis section.
- Series X. ROSEMARY REYNOLDS PAPERS 1901-1986, 1 ft., 6 in.
  This series is arranged in five sections and follows a chronological order within each area. The first section contains biographical material about Reynolds and her family. The second section, correspondence, consists of a few letters generated between 1922 and 1984. The education section holds papers and notes from the various educational institutions Reynolds attended. Her Master of Social Work thesis, "Casework for First Years," is housed here. The fourth section, "Publications, Papers, and Speeches, begins with issues of The Spokesman written by Reynolds and includes other papers and publication from the early 1930s through 1959. The series concludes with materials related to Reynolds' professional activities. These include agency records, studies and reports, notes on conferences and seminars, and material on supervision. The agency records were chiefly generated at the Community Service Society of New York, where Reynolds was employed for twenty-nine years.
- Series I. BIOGRAPHICAL
  - Family papers and personal material
    - Certificate of draft exemption, William Hollis, 1863 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Bertha Hoerig's graduation materials, Pierce School, 1893 (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Bertha Hoerig's anniversary book, 1901-1957 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Family register, covers 1790 to 1925 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Hoerig family genealogy, covers 1833 to 1972 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Marriage certificate, Bertha Hoerig and Louis Hollis, 1905 (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Florence Hollis's confirmation paper, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Biographical material, 1937-1986 (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Hollis wedding anniversary invitation, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Wisconsin Audubon Camp, Florence Hollis and Rosemary Reynolds, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - "To read," and reading notes, ca. 1970-1979 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - Medical records, 1971-ca. 1980s (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Retirement, cards, correspondence, tribute, ca. 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Political affiliations and interests, correspondence and assorted documents, ca. 1941, ca. 1974-1986 (Box 1, Folder 14)
    - Certificates, appointments and award, 1950-1983, undated (Box 1, Folder 15)
    - Passport, 1976-1978 (Box 1, Folder 16)
    - Newsclippings on William, Louis and Charles Hollis, undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Education
    - Philadelphia High School for Girls
      - Valedictory address and transcript, 1924-1928 (Box 1, Folder 18)
    - Wellesley College
      - Junior Month material, July 1927 (Box 1, Folder 19)
      - Thesis, "The Slavery Controversy in the Methodist Episcopal Church," 1928 (Box 1, Folder 20)
      - Thesis, correspondence, 1929 (Box 1, Folder 21)
    - Pennsylvania School of Social Work
      - School papers and related correspondence, ca. 1929 (Box 2, Folder 22)
    - Smith College School for Social Work
      - Course descriptions, ca. 1930 (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - Bryn Mawr College
      - Reading notes, 1940-1941 (Box 2, Folder 24)
      - "A Study of Aggression in Two Primitive Cultures," 1941 (Box 2, Folder 25)
      - Papers, abnormal psychology, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 26)
      - Ph.D. exam, 1942 (Box 2, Folder 27)
      - Dissertation, "Casework in Marital Disharmony,"
        - Chapters 1-6, 1947-1951 (Box 2, Folder 28)
        - Chapters 7-11, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 29)
        - Chapters 12-14 and Appendices, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 30)
    - Neurological Institute, lectures 1-4, Dr. van Ophuijsen, transcript and notes, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 31)
    - Community Service Society of New York, seminar, notes, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 32)
    - Community Service Society of New York, Dr. Werner's seminar, case records, minutes and notes, 1950-1951 (Box 2, Folder 33)
    - New York School of Social Work
      - Statistics course with Professor Wiggins
        - First session, Fall 1961 (Box 2, Folder 34)
        - 1962 (Box 2, Folder 35)
        - Course material with related correspondence, ca. 1964-1966 (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - New York Psychoanalytic Institute, lecture, Anna Freud, "Difficulties in the Path of Psychoanalysis," program and notes, 1968 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Retirement
    - Kendal at Longwood, correspondence and related materials, 1972-1975 (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Correspondence concerning Crosslands, ca. 1975-1977 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Committees at Crosslands
      - Board-dinner committee, memos, notes and correspondence, ca. 1978-1980 (Box 3, Folder 40)
      - Residents Association Board records, 1979-ca. 1984 (Box 3, Folder 41)
      - Liaison Services Committee records, 1980-1986 (Box 3, Folder 42)
      - Friends of Audland-Firbank records, 1981-1984 (Box 3, Folder 43)
      - TirLawyn records and correspondence, ca. 1983-1986 (Box 3, Folder 44)
      - Art Exhibit Committee records, 1984-1985 (Box 3, Folder 45)
    - Crosslands Chronicle, 1978-1986 (Box 3, Folder 46)
    - Recreational activities, ca. 1976-1981, undated (Box 3, Folder 47)
    - Garden plans, 1977-ca. 1980 (Box 3, Folder 48)
    - Music, annotated concert programs and dulcimer fellowship newsletter, 1980-1984 (Box 3, Folder 49)
    - Hospice workshop, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 50)
    - Swissair award, newsclippings, photo, press release, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 51)
    - Living with stress workshop, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 52)
    - Desk calendar, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 53)
    - Inspirational materials, ca. 1980s, undated (Box 3, Folder 54)
  - Florence Hollis and the Development of Psychosocial Casework Theory: An Intellectual Biography, 1927-1940 (dissertation, 1980) by Stacia Super
    - Correspondence, extracts from college course catalogs, and transcripts, 1928-1943, 1976-1979 (Box 3, Folder 55)
    - Clare Tousley and Junior Month, corresponence and clipping, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 56)
    - Betsey Libbey, correspondence and photocopy of a Smith School for Social Work report, 1940-1941, 1977 (Box 3, Folder 57)
    - Bibliographies of references to Florence Hollis and her work, 1976, undated (Box 3, Folder 58)
    - Articles and notes by Florence Hollis, 1931-1938, ca. 1980 (Box 3, Folder 59)
    - Biographical material, correspondence, articles, and other printed material, 1941-1977, undated (Box 3, Folder 60)
    - "Introductory Biography of Florence Hollis and a Guide to Interviewing," by Stacia Super, January 1977 (Box 3, Folder 61)
    - Taped interviews by Stacia Super, typescripts and notes, 1976-1978 (Box 3, Folder 62)
    - Interviews, Florence Hollis and Stacia Super, 5 cassette tapes, 1977-1978 (Box 3)
    - Typescript (photocopy), 1980 (Box 3, Folder 63)
    - "New pages," August 1980 (Box 3a, Folder 64)
    - Extracts from dissertation with comments by F. Hollis, ca. 1980 (Box 3a, Folder 65)
    - "Mostly just ideas," with comments by F. Hollis, ca. 1980 (Box 3a, Folder 66)
    - "Factual matters," ca. 1980 (Box 3a, Folder 67)
    - Corrections, 1980 (Box 3a, Folder 68)
  - Oral histories
    - "A Series of Interviews with Florence Hollis," by Vida S. Grayson, 1985
      - Typescript, copyright 1993 by Smith College (2 copies) and introductory material (Box 3a, Folder 69)
      - Cassette tape, [digital copy available] (Box 3a)
      - Florence Hollis and Rosemary Reynolds interviewed by Ann Hartman, 28 October 1970: 2 tapes (one is a duplicate) (Box 3a)
        [digital copy available (poor audio quality)]
- Series II. CORRESPONDENCE
  - Personal correspondence
    - Correspondence from Florence Hollis, undated (Box 3a, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence with friends and relatives (Box 3a)
      - 1965-ca. 1979 (Box 3a, Folder 2)
      - 1980-1984 (Box 3a, Folder 3)
      - ca. 1985-1986 (Box 3a, Folder 4)
      - Frank and Naomi March, 1970 (Box 3a, Folder 5)
      - Frank March, ca. 1971 (Box 3a, Folder 6)
      - Frank March, ca. 1972 (Box 3a, Folder 7)
      - Frank March, ca. 1973 (Box 4, Folder 8)
      - Frank March, ca. 1974 (Box 4, Folder 9)
      - Frank March, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 10)
      - Frank March, 1976-1977 (Box 4, Folder 11)
      - Frank March, ca. 1970-1977 (Box 4, Folder 12)
      - Inga Gottfarb, 1967-1986, undated (Box 4, Folder 13)
      - Dame Eileen Younghusband, 1972-1981, undated (Box 4, Folder 14)
      - Anni Hofer and Ruth Zobrist, ca. 1964, 1978-1986 (Box 4, Folder 15)
      - Anni Hofer memorial, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 16)
      - Ruth Schwarz's gift of Rosemary Reynolds' letters, 1962-1964, 1983, undated (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - Student correspondence, 1946-1974, undated (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Undated correspondence (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - General correspondence
      - ca. 1933-1939, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 20)
      - 1940-1942 (Box 4, Folder 21)
      - 1945-1949 (Box 4, Folder 22)
      - 1950-1954 (Box 4, Folder 23)
      - ca. 1955-1959 (Box 4, Folder 24)
      - 1962-1965 (Box 4, Folder 25)
      - 1966-1969 (Box 4, Folder 26)
      - 1969 (Box 5, Folder 27)
      - 1970-1973 (Box 5, Folder 28)
      - 1973 (Box 5, Folder 29)
      - ca. 1974-1975 (Box 5, Folder 30)
      - 1976-1977 (Box 5, Folder 31)
      - ca. 1977 (Box 5, Folder 32)
      - 1978-ca. 1980 (Box 5, Folder 33)
      - 1980-1981 (Box 5, Folder 34)
      - 1982-1983 (Box 5, Folder 35)
      - 1984-1986 (Box 5, Folder 36)
      - Undated (Box 5, Folder 37)
      - Judith Mishne, correspondence and other documents, ca. 1978-1979. (Box 5, Folder 38)
        Closed to use until Mishne's death or 2044.
      - Random House, 1962-1979 (Box 6, Folder 39)
      - Random House, 1980-1986, undated (Box 6, Folder 40)
      - Stacia Super, 1976-1980 (Box 6, Folder 41)
      - Mary Woods, correspondence and notes, ca. 1977-1981, 1986 (Box 6, Folder 42)
      - Correspondence records, 1942-1985 (Box 6, Folder 43)
  - Correspondence, tributes and newsclippings concerning social work professionals and friends
    - Betsey Libbey, biographical materials and related documents, 1938-1985, undated (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - Mary E. Richmond, assorted documents, 1909, 1963, ca. 1985, undated (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - Social work professsionals and friends of Florence Hollis and Rosemary Reynolds, newsclippings, tributes and related documents, ca. 1932-1982, undated (Box 6, Folder 46)
- Series III. EMPLOYMENT AND PROFESSIONAL WORK
  - Family Society of Philadelphia
    - "A Brief History of Family Service of Philadelphia: 1879-1972," Ralph Ormsby, undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Committee on content of "therapeutic" casework, minutes, 1932-1933, ca. 1986 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - "What is a Reasonable Caseload?," 1939 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Family Society of Rochester, New York
    - Study and correspondence, 1939-1940, 1985 (Box 6)
  - Family Service Association of America (formerly Family Welfare Association of America)
    - Annual meeting, 1935 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Committee on professional education, reports and related materials, ca. 1938-1947 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Director of publication services, assorted materials, 1941-ca. 1947 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Family casework, assorted documents, 1943-1954 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - "Patterns in Use of Family Agency Service," Dorothy Beck, published report and related materials, ca. 1961-1962 (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - "Private Social Welfare's Disengagement from the Poor: The Case of Family Adjustment Agencies," Richard Cloward, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 10)
      - Memoranda and other documents relating to Clowards's paper, 1964-ca. 1965 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Publications, 1946, 1959 (Box 7, Folder 12)
    - Reports, assorted, 1937-1972 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Community Service Society of New York
    - DSS study, questionnaire and related materials, 1958-ca. 1977, ca. 1986 (Box 7, Folder 14)
    - Research project proposal, correspondence and report, ca. 1974 (Box 7, Folder 15)
      [see also Flat file]
    - Miscellaneous, ca. 1966-1978 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Council on Social Work Education (formerly American Association of Schools of Social Work)
    - Advisory committee on advanced education in social work
      - Minutes, 1962-1963 (Box 7, Folder 17)
      - Non-school programs, memos and related documents, 1962-1964 (Box 7, Folder 18)
      - Subcommittee on clinical emphasis, assorted reports, 1962-1966 (Box 7, Folder 19)
      - Subcommittee on preparation of teachers, papers and reports, ca. 1964-1965 (Box 7, Folder 20)
    - Annual meeting, report and related documents, 1949 (Box 7, Folder 21)
    - Annual meeting, report, ca. 1950 (Box 7, Folder 22)
    - Discussion by Ruth Smalley, 1959 (Box 7, Folder 23)
    - Educational Consultation Service, committee records, 1981-1982 (Box 7, Folder 24)
    - Report and minutes, 1953-1954 (Box 7, Folder 25)
    - Stein committee report and related materials, ca. 1966-1971 (Box 7, Folder 26)
    - Task force on structure and quality in social work education, comments and correspondence, 1974-1975 (Box 7, Folder 27)
    - Miscellaneous, 1971-1985 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - National Association of Social Workers, proposals, position statement and correspondence, ca. 1960-1985 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Client advisory committee, memos, 1966-1967 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Parents of retarded adults meeting, printed material and correspondence, 1966-1973, undated (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Bryn Mawr advisory committee, memos, minutes, correspondence and notes, 1979-1985 (Box 7, Folder 32)
- Series IV. TEACHING
  - Western Reserve University, School of Applied Social Sciences
    - Course material
      - Bibliographies, ca. 1930-1939, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 1)
      - Case work II
        - Lecture notes, 1934-1935, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 2)
        - Lecture notes, 1934-1936, 1983 (Box 8, Folder 3)
        - Lecture notes, 1937, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 4)
        - Student cases and papers, 1934-1935, ca. 1985 (Box 8, Folder 5)
        - Student cases, 1937-1940, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 6)
      - Student cases and papers, interviewing course, 1935-1936, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 7)
      - Supervision, conferences notes used in supervision class, 1936-1942, 1986 (Box 8, Folder 8)
      - "Classification of Theses of Family Case Work Students," ca. 1934, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - Cases
      - Used in teaching
        - Deimer, 1935-ca. 1940, ca. 1985 (Box 8, Folder 10)
        - Dorsey, 1939-ca. 1940s, ca. 1985 (Box 8, Folder 11)
        - Dostoevski, ca. 1933-1940, ca. 1985 (Box 8, Folder 12)
        - Lynch, ca. 1935, ca. 1985 (Box 8, Folder 13)
        - Morazzo, 1926-1933, ca. 1985 (Box 8, Folder 14)
        - Patrick, 1934, ca. 1985 (Box 8, Folder 15)
        - Peter, 1933, undated (Box 8, Folder 16)
        - Stolarski, 1934-1935, ca. 1986, undated (Box 8, Folder 17)
        - Taylor, 1933, ca. 1940s, ca. 1985 (Box 8, Folder 18)
        - Wilkins and Wilson, 1933, ca. 1985 (Box 8, Folder 19)
        - York, ca. 1930s, ca. 1950s, ca. 1986 (Box 8, Folder 20)
      - Not used in teaching
        - Doman, 1934, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 21)
        - Williamson, ca. 1930s, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 22)
      - Miscellaneous
        - Florence R. Day, lecture notes, articles and memo, ca. 1934-1957, ca. 1986 (Box 9, Folder 23)
        - "A Study of Professional Education for Social Work in Cleveland," Dorothy Kahn, 1938 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - New York School of Social Work (becomes Columbia University School of Social Work in 1962)
    - Course material
      - Bibliographies, course 123 and 124, ca. 1950-1965, undated (Box 9, Folder 25)
      - Bibliographies, course 128, 1957-1965 (Box 9, Folder 26)
      - Course assignments, assorted, 1956-1971, undated (Box 9, Folder 27)
      - Casework 1 and/or 2, lecture notes, ca. 1944-1952 (Box 9, Folder 28)
      - Casework 1 and/or 2, lecture notes, ca. 1955-1957 (Box 9, Folder 29)
      - Casework 1 and/or 2, lecture notes, ca. 1958-1970 (Box 9, Folder 30)
      - Casework 1 and/or 2, lecture notes and course material, ca. 1969-1971 (Box 9, Folder 31)
      - Casework 1, supplementary lecture material, 1917-1970 (Box 9, Folder 32)
      - Casework 2, lecture notes, memoranda and related materials, ca. 1946-1963 (Box 9, Folder 33)
      - Casework 1 (course 120 and 121), syllabi and assignments, ca. 1952-1954 (Box 9, Folder 34)
      - Casework 1 and/or 2, memoranda, minutes and related material, 1952-1969 (Box 9, Folder 35)
      - Casework 1 (course 121), social study outlines and related material, ca. 1959-1971 (Box 10, Folder 36)
      - Casework 3 and 4, lecture notes and related material, ca. 1951-1960 (Box 10, Folder 37)
      - Casework 4 and 6, lecture notes and related materials, ca. 1947-1965 (Box 10, Folder 38)
      - Course 220, course description, lecture notes, minutes, ca. 1952-1954 (Box 10, Folder 39)
      - Course 220, lecture notes and related material, ca. 1953-1962 (Box 10, Folder 40)
      - Course 220, lecture notes, ca. 1962-1965 (Box 10, Folder 41)
      - Course 6202[?], material from Barbara Wilkerson, memoranda and process records, 1969-1970 (Box 10, Folder 42)
      - Classification system, early lecture notes, ca. 1953-1956 (Box 10, Folder 43)
      - Course [8201?], social class, notes on reading material and book reviews, ca. 1966-1970, undated (Box 10, Folder 44)
      - Course 8201, classification resource materials, ca. 1966-1970 (Box 10, Folder 45)
      - Course 8201-[2?], lecture notes, ca. 1969-1970 (Box 11, Folder 46)
      - Course 8201-[2?], lecture notes and course assignments, ca. 1970-1971 (Box 11, Folder 47)
      - Course T-8202, scattered lecture notes, ca. 1964-1970 (Box 11, Folder 48)
      - Course T-8202, lecture notes, 1968 (Box 11, Folder 49)
      - Family casework, lecture notes and related material, ca. 1946-1961, ca. 1985 (Box 11, Folder 50)
      - Casework and psychotherapy, lecture notes and related materials, ca. 1949-1959 (Box 11, Folder 51)
      - Field work in casework, reports and syllabus, 1949-1955, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 52)
      - Generic and specific factors in casework, notes, bibliographies and student presentation, ca. 1954-1955, ca. 1986 (Box 11, Folder 53)
      - Cases used in teaching, records and notes, ca. 1958-1970, undated (Box 11, Folder 54)
      - System theory notes, ca. 1968 (Box 11, Folder 55)
    - Student cases related to coursework
      - Course 220, records and notes, ca. 1958-1960 (Box 11, Folder 56)
      - Records and notes, ca. 1960-1963 (Box 11, Folder 57)
      - Casework 1, case record and notes, ca. 1967-1970 (Box 12, Folder 58)
      - Course 6202, records and notes, ca. 1969-1970 (Box 12, Folder 59)
      - Course 6202, records and notes, ca. 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 60)
      - Course 6208 and T6208, records and notes, ca. 1970-1971 (Box 12, Folder 61)
    - Student papers
      - Assorted, ca. 1957-1967 (Box 12, Folder 62)
      - Assorted, 1971 (Box 12, Folder 63)
      - "Follow up Report on an Institutionalized Child," master's thesis, n.a., 1955 (Box 12, Folder 64)
      - "Some Aspects of Obesity, Depression and Separation," Mary Scully, ca. 1962-1967 (Box 12, Folder 65)
      - Family Casework, ca. 1958-1962 (Box 12, Folder 66)
      - Course 104, 1947-1951 (Box 12, Folder 67)
      - Course 121, 1953-1967 (Box 12, Folder 68)
      - Course 124, 1961-1965 (Box 12, Folder 69)
      - Course 128, ca. 1955-1960 (Box 12, Folder 70)
      - Course 128, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 71)
      - Course 128, 1965 (Box 13, Folder 72)
      - Course 220, 1956-1958 (Box 13, Folder 73)
      - Course 220, 1959 (Box 13, Folder 74)
      - Course 220, ca. 1960-1963 (Box 13, Folder 75)
      - Course 220, ca. 1964-1965 (Box 13, Folder 76)
      - Course 221, ca. 1957 (Box 13, Folder 77)
      - Course 6201 and 6202, ca. 1968-1971 (Box 13, Folder 78)
      - Course T6208, 1966 (Box 13, Folder 79)
      - Course T8201, "Some Aspects of Comparative Casework Theory and the Theory of General Systems," Rosemary Lukton, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 80)
      - Course 8202 amd T8202, 1968-1969 (Box 14, Folder 81)
      - Course T8202, "Differential Factors in Direct Casework Treatment of the Aging," Barbara Silverstone, 1969 (Box 14, Folder 82)
      - For various professors, ca. 1958-1967 (Box 14, Folder 83)
      - For various professors, ca. 1968 (Box 14, Folder 84)
      - For Professor Kristenson, course T8201, "Stimulus Hunger in the Aged and the Implication for Casework Theory and Practice," Barbara Silverstone, 1968-1969 (Box 14, Folder 85)
      - Bibliographies from student papers, ca. 1958-1963 (Box 14, Folder 86)
    - Miscellaneous
      - Casework committees, notes, minutes and related material, ca. 1950-1964 (Box 14, Folder 87)
      - Student placement and advisees, 1968-1975, undated (Box 14, Folder 88)
      - Anni Hofer's notes from Hollis's courses, casework 1 and casework 2, 1950, ca. 1985 (Box 14, Folder 89)
      - Anni Hofer, United Nations fellow, monthly progress reports and final report, 1950 (Box 14, Folder 90)
  - Smith College School for Social Work
    - "Casework in Marital Counseling" seminar
      - Case records and notes